<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>meetup on GoManila</title>
    <link>https://www.gomanila.org/categories/meetup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in meetup on GoManila</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 14:24:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gomanila.org/categories/meetup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RSVP now for the January 2020 meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2020.01.meetup.rsvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 14:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2020.01.meetup.rsvp/</guid>
      <description>Happy 2020, folks! We&amp;rsquo;re kicking off the new year with our first meetup. This January 13 we&amp;rsquo;ll be at WeWork Uptown BGC with two speakers from Brankas. The meetup would be great for beginners and advanced developers in Go. Don&amp;rsquo;t know anything about the language? There&amp;rsquo;s something for you too!
If you&amp;rsquo;re a Go newbie or are interested on learning the language, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to listen to Junior Systems Engineer Carlos Daroya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoManila Mondays! - 10.19 meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.10.meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 21:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.10.meetup/</guid>
      <description>We had a blast at the meetup last night as always! We apologize for the sound suddenly disappearing every now and then during livestream. We&amp;rsquo;ll make sure to fix that next time. Nevertheless, we hope you enjoyed the night&amp;rsquo;s meetup. If you missed last night, here&amp;rsquo;s the link to the meetup video.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to subscribe to our YouTube channel!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSVP now for the October meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.10.rsvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.10.rsvp/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in using Go in your company but need more information from people who are already using it in the enterprise? This October we&amp;rsquo;ll look at two companies and discover how they use Go in their systems. Both Johnny Estilles (Director of Engineering, Freelancer.com) and Miguel Martinez (System Developer, Brankas) will be discussing why they decided to use the language and the results of going for a technology that not many are locally using at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoManila Mondays! - 09.19 meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.09.meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 20:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.09.meetup/</guid>
      <description>This month we had Andre Marcelo-Tanner, Senior Site Reliability Engineer at Ada Support Inc; and Johnny Estilles, Regional Director of Engineering at Freelancer.com.
Andre talked about devising a single way to leverage Go to develop, deploy and monitor applications. Johnny explored the different usecases of Websockets in the context of the Go programming language.
  If the video is not showing up, please visit this link instead </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoManila - 08.19 meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.08.meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gomanila.org/blog/2019.08.meetup/</guid>
      <description>This August we had Gin Galang, Python Developer at Willis Towers Watson; and Jorick Caberio, Software Engineer at Voyager Innovations Inc.
Gin talked about building blockchain using Go and how it can benefit you, while Jorick shared how to implement a GSM protocol to send and receive SMS using Go.
  If the video is not showing up, please visit this link instead </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>